{
    question:
    "1. Which of the following is not a product in the Alcatel-Lucent 7750 SR/7450 ESS family?",
    choice1: 'SR-12',
    choice2: 'ESS-7',
    choice3: 'SR-6',
    choice4: 'ESS-1',
    answer: 3,
    },
    {
    question:
    "2. Which of the following statements is false regarding the Alcatel-Lucent 7450 ESS series?",
    choice1: 'It supports multiple chassis types.',
    choice2: 'It supports OSFP, IS-IS, RIP, and BGP.',
    choice3: 'It is used primarily for Ethernet aggregation.',
    choice4: 'It can be managed via a console port or a dedicated Ethernet port on the SF/CPM.',
    answer: 2,
    },
    {
    question:
    "3. Which of the following descriptions is correct?",
    choice1: 'bof.cfg—7750/7450 configuration file',
    choice2: 'cpm.tim—IOM image file',
    choice3: 'config.cfg—Back-up configuration file',
    choice4: 'boot.ldr—Bootstrap image file',
    answer: 4,
    },
    {
    question:
    "4. Which of the following commands is not correctly described?",
    choice1: 'shutdown—This command is used to disable an interface or protocol.',
    choice2: 'exit all—Logs out of the Alcatel-Lucent 7750 SR/7450 ESS device.',
    choice3: '?—Lists all commands in the current context.',
    choice4: '[TAB]—This command is used for assistance with command completion.',
    answer: 2,
    },
    {
    question:
    "5. Which of the following is not a log stream type?",
    choice1: 'Audit',
    choice2: 'Change',
    choice3: 'Main',
    choice4: 'Security',
    answer: 1,
    },
    {
    question:
    "6. Which of the following descriptions of hardware for the Alcatel-Lucent 7750 SR/7450 ESS is correct?",
    choice1: 'IOMs plug into MDAs.',
    choice2: 'MDAs plug into SFPs.',
    choice3: 'SF/CPMs plug into IOMs.',
    choice4: 'IOMs plug into the chassis.',
    answer: 4,
    },
    {
    question:
    "7. What file contains the system bootstrap image?",
    choice1: 'boot.cfg',
    choice2: 'image.ldr',
    choice3: 'boot.ldr',
    choice4: 'bof.cfg',
    answer: 3,
    },
    {
    question:
    "8. The SF/CPM card has its own Ethernet interface for out-of-band management. This interface has its own IP address and default route. Where is this information stored?",
    choice1: 'boot.ldf',
    choice2: 'bof.cfg',
    choice3: 'config.cfg',
    choice4: 'cpm.tim',
    answer: 2,
    },
    {
    question:
    "9. Which of the following correctly lists the order in which files are read by the Alcatel-Lucent 7750 SR/7450 ESS upon bootup?",
    choice1: 'boot.ldr, bof.cfg, system image, config.cfg',
    choice2: 'system image, boot.ldr, config.cfg, bof.cfg',
    choice3: 'boot.ldr, system image, bof.cfg, config.cfg',
    choice4: 'boot.ldr, bof.cfg, config.cfg, system image',
    answer: 1,
    },
    {
    question:
    "10. During the boot process, an Alcatel-Lucent 7750 SR/7450 ESS checks to see if persistence is enablechoice4: 'What is the purpose of persistence?",
    choice1: 'To ensure that the system saves routing table information when it reboots',
    choice2: 'To ensure that changes to the bof.cfg are saved',
    choice3: 'To ensure synchronization with the 5620 SAM',
    choice4: 'To ensure that config changes are stored in the config.cfg',
    answer: 3,
    },
    {
    question:
    "11. What command would you use to enable an interface the first time you initialized an Alcatel-Lucent 7750 SR/7450 ESS?",
    choice1: 'enable',
    choice2: 'no shutdown',
    choice3: 'interface enable',
    choice4: 'interface on',
    answer: 2
    },
    {
    question:
    "12. Which of the following is the correct provisioning order you should follow when configuring an Alcatel-Lucent 7750 SR/7450 ESS for the first time?",
    choice1: 'IOM, port, MDA',
    choice2: 'Port, MDA, IOM',
    choice3: 'IOM, MDA, port',
    choice4: 'MDA, port, IOM',
    answer: 3,
    },
    {
    question:
    "13. Which of the following is false regarding the logging mechanisms in the AlcatelLucent 7750 SR/7450 ESS?",
    choice1: 'Log-ids 99 and 100 are reserved for system usage.',
    choice2: ' You must configure at least one input stream for a log-id',
    choice3: 'You must configure a filter for each log-id',
    choice4: 'You must configure the destination for the events from the log-id',
    answer: 3,
    },
    {
    question:
    "14. What command would you use to display the configuration of your Alcatel-Lucent 7750 SR/7450 ESS?",
    choice1: 'show config',
    choice2: 'admin display-config',
    choice3: 'display config',
    choice4: 'show admin config',
    answer: 2,
    },
    {
    question:
    "15. Which of the following values is not stored in the bof.cfg?",
    choice1: 'The location of the primary boot image',
    choice2: 'The list of IOM cards in the chassis',
    choice3: 'The persist value',
    choice4: 'The location of the primary config file',
    answer: 2,
    }
    